Finding Aid for francisco
Clarke Historical Library
Francisco Photography Studio Photographic collection, 1910-1990, and undated
Francisco Photography Studio.
9 cubic feet (in 9 boxes, 1 Oversized folder)
MSS.
The collection includes mostly black and white photographs and negatives in various sizes documenting multiple generations of hundreds of families from the Mount Pleasant, Michigan, area and nearby locales..
Clarke Historical Library, Central Michigan University
Acc# 3163, 39131
Francisco Photography Studio Photographic collection is open for research.
Biography:
The Francisco Photography Studio was operated on West Broadway in Mount Pleasant, Michigan, by a father and son team, Harry H. and Harrison Francisco, for 68 years.
Harry H. “Poddy” Francisco was born on August 10, 1891 in Mount Pleasant, to Charles and Mabel Francisco. In 1910, he married Lillian Belle Alexander of Gaylord, Michigan. They had two children, Harrison, and Mrs. Verona Sutton, both of Mount Pleasant.
Harry entered the photography business at age 19 and worked until eight weeks before his death. An avid outdoorsman, he also enjoyed novelty woodwork and was a member of the Elks Lodge. On August 14, 1944, Harry died at his home on South Fancher. He was survived by his wife, children, mother, and one granddaughter, Elrae Mayville.
Harrison A. Francisco was born on August 14, 1911 in Mount Pleasant. Except or service in the U.S. Army during World War II, he worked all of his life in the photography studio, from which he retired in 1973. Like his father, Harrison was an avid hunter and fisherman. He never married. He died on December 2, 1990 and was survived by his sister. (This information is from the collection.)
Arrangement is The collection is organized as it was created, with negatives and photographs separated by media, then by size, and then either alphabetically by customers’ surname or by date.
The collection includes mostly black and white photographs and negatives, circa 1910-1990, in various sizes hosued in envelopes, no folders. Several generations of local families are documented in the collection through family portraits, first communion, wedding, high school graduation, identification, and armed service photographs. Other topics include sports teams, marriage licenses, service discharge certificates, hunting and fishing, buildings, art, vehicles, and a burn victim, among others. There may be more than one view of an image, Ex. - 2, and more than one sleeve or envelope of images on a topic or a person, Ex. (2 envelopes). There are eight folders of Francisco family photographs and negatives in the back of Box 9. A folder of biographical information on the Franciscos and mostly World War II postcards is in the front of Box 1. Oversized photographs (4) are also of the Francisco family. Some of the photographs are copies of images from the turn of the 19th/20th century.
The collection is organized as it was created, with negatives and photographs separated by media, then by size, and then either alphabetically by customers’ surname or by date as follows: Box 1- 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G; Box 2- 5 x 7 inch Negatives, H-R; Box 3- 5 x 7 inch Negatives, S-Z; Box 4- 3.5x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gr; Box 5- 3.5x 4.5 inch Negatives, Gr-R; Box 6- 3.5x4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z; Miscellaneous Smaller Photos: 5.5 x 7.25 inches Photographs and Negatives; Box 7- 8 x 10 inch Negatives; Box 8- 8 x 10 inch Photographs, 1961-1970; 5.5 x 6 inch Photographs, 1958-1965; Box 9- 5.5 x 6 inch Photographs, 1965-1969; 3.5 x 4 inch and Smaller Sized Photographs and Negatives, 1917-1958; Francisco Family Photographs, 1927-1964 and undated; Negatives, undated; Oversized folder Francisco Family (4 Oversized prints). Any additional notes or abbreviations are taken from the original wrappers and were made by the photographers.
Subjects:
Francisco, Harrison A., 1911-1990.; Francisco, Harry H., 1891-1944.; Francisco Photography Studio.; Photographers--Michigan--Mount Pleasant.; Mount Pleasant (Mich.)--History.; Mount Pleasant (Mich.)--Genealogy.
- Francisco Photography Studio Photographic Collection is open for research.
  - Biographical Materials,1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Abbey, Oma,undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Abbey, Oma, I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Abbott, Marshall, Sr. (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Abbott, Marshall - Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Abbott, Marshall and Wife,Christmas 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Abbott, Mickey - 2 children,undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Abbott, Wayne - 4 children,undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Abby, Ron and Wife,undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Acker, Ken - Wedding (3 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Acne, I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Albar, Al,undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Albee, J. A. - Baby Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Albee, J. A. - Family,undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Albee, Jack - Daughter,undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Albee, Jack - Daughter and Wife,undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Aldrich, J. C. - Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Aldrich, J. C. - Girl and Boy,undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Alexander, Minnie - Copy,August 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Allen, Barbara - 3 boys,undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Allen, Barbara,undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Allen, Donna - H.S.,undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Allen, Katie,undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Allen, Leona,undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Allen, Woody,undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Anderson, Claudie,undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Anderson, Dale - Wedding,undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Anderson, Loren - Wedding (3 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Anthony, Wayne - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Archey, Ed (Mrs.) - Copy,January 5, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Armstrong, Shirley,undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Arnold, James - Copy,June 17, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Art Photographs, Francisco,undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ash, Alvin - 1-year-old,undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ash, Alvin - 1- and 2-year-old Children,undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ash, Alvin - 1-year-old, 9th month,1961 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ash, Alvin - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ash, Shirley - 1-year-old,March 5, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ashquab, Rosie - Copies,undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Askegard, H. L. - (3 babies),undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Askegard, Harry - 1- and 2-year-old,March 21, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Aungst, Don - H.S.,undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Austin, Marge,undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Avery, Lloyd - 9-month-old,undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Avery, Lloyd,undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bader, Geo. - Baby,undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bader, Geo. - 1st Communion,undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bader, Geo. - Copy,undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bader, Geo. - 13th-month-old,undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bailey, Fred - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bailey, Nancy,undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bailey, Sue - I.D.undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Baker, LeRoy,1966 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Baldwin, Tripto (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ball, Bob - H.S. (Robert H.),undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ball, Bob - Family,undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ball, Florence,undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ball, Jack,undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ball, Leonard - Copy,undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Ball, Ruth,undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bardaville, John (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Barker, Geneva,undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Barnes, Caralane,undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Barrett, Clarence - (2),undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Barrett, Joyce,undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Barton, Phylis,undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bates, Janice - 5-month,undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Battle Motor Company Bowling,1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Baugham, Laura - I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bauman, Gerald - 1-year-old Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bauman, Ted - Copyundated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Baumann, Mable,undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Baxter, (Miss) - (Copy - Earl Peterson),undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Baxter, Neva - (Copy - Mrs. Warick),undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Beck, Andy,undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Beck, G. L. - Copy,undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Beckrend, Wm., Jr. - 3 children,undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Beerman, Gerald - 2- and 4-year-olds,undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Behrend, [no first name] - I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Belint, Anna - Copy (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Belle, Lillian - I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bellinger, [no first name] - Copy,undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bellinger, [no first name] - Bride (Chas. McConnell Daughter),undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bellinger, Cecil - 4 Generations,undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bellinger, Kathryn,undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Belsin, Betty,undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Benfard, Joch - Copy,undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bergman, Belva - I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bierschback, E.,undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bierschback, Eugene - 6- and 8-year-olds,November 14, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bierschback, Eugene - 1st Communion - Girl,May 4, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bierschback, James - Copy,undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bierschback, Pat - Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Billsby, Roy - 2-year-old,undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bissett, Carol - H.S.,undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bissett, Sharon - H.S.,undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bissette, Viola, I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bixby, Ed - 3 Children,Christmas 1949 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bixby, Ed,Christmas 1948 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bixby, John - 3 Children,undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Black, Delores,undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Blackman, Ann,undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Blackman, E. and Wife - 50th Anniversary,October 12, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bland, A. T. - Trooper (Michigan State Police),undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Blizzard, Jeann,undated (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Boder, Geo. -1st Communion - Girl,1960 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bollman, D. - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bollman, Ken - 4 Children and Mother,undated (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bollman, Ken - 4 Children,undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bollman, Ken - Twin Girls -1-year-old,undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bollman, (Mrs.), Sr.,undated (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bondy, [no first name] - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bonnell, Ed Jr. Copy (2 envelopes)undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Border, Geo. - Baby (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bordine, Barbara Ann - Copy,undated (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Borle, Ray,undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bourland, Jim - Family -Copy,undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bourland, Jim, Jr.,undated (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bourland, Joanne,undated (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bourland, Joanne - H.S.,undated (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bourland, Sharron,undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bousbey, Cris, - I.D.,November 3, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Boussum, C.,undated (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bowser, Wm. - 2-year-old,undated (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brandt Electronics (3 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Branson, Orville (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brazington, [no first name] - Copy,undated (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brecht, Marjorie (Mrs.) - 1-year-old Boy and 3-year-old Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brecht, Marjorie (Mrs.) - 1-year-old Boy,undated (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brecht, Richard - 1-year-old Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brecht, Richard - 3 Children,undated (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brewer, Matt - and Wife,undated (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brickner, Dale - 14-month-old,undated (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brock, Valeria,undated (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brondstetter, Joe -2.5-year-old Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brondstetter, Joe -2.5-year-old Girl with 3.5-year-old Ronald Warners,undated (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brown, Betty,undated (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brown, Cedrie - Boy, 1st Communion,undated (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brown, Cedrie,1954 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brown, Cedrie, I.D.undated (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brown, R.L.,undated (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brown, Ronald -I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Brunson, R. -I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Buffard, Jean,undated (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bugbee, Bertha,undated (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bugbee, Lewis,undated (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bullard, Alden - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Builders Supply Company,1940 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bullard, Ed - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bullard, Ray - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bundy, Wm. (Mrs.) - Copy of His Last Will and Testament (3 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bundy, William - and Wife,undated (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bunker, Joyce,undated (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bunker, Larry,1963 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bunker, Larry - H.S.,1961 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bunker, Walter (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bunting, Oral - and Wife,undated (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Burch, Jim - H.S.,undated (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Burned Victim,undated (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bush, Joe (Mrs.) - 1.5-year-old Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bushong, Ben,undated (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bushong, Marvel - H.S.,undated (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bushong, Patricia - H.S.,undated (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Bushong, Shirley,undated (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Byrd, Paulette - 8-week-old Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Byrd, Pauline - 2-year-old,June 11, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Caldwell, K.,undated (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Calkins, [no first name],September 17, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Calkins, Wm. and Wife,undated (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Campbell, [no first name],undated (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Campbell, Beverly,1951 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Campbell, Beverly,1954 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Campbell, Connie,undated (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Campbell, Hugh,May 1939 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Campbell, Lawrence B. - (3),undated (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Campbell, Robt. - Baby Boy,undated (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Campbell, Robt. - 2 Boys,undated (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Canute, Clair - 9-month-old,undated (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Canute, Glen L. - Army Discharge,undated (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Carey, Ed and Wife (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Carey, Richard - 1st Communion,1961/1962 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Carey, Richard- 4 year-old boy,undated (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Carmichael, Duncan - and Wife,undated (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Carnaham, Tip,September 5, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Carnaham, Tip (Mrs.),September 5, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Carr, Guy (Mrs.),November 5, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Carroll, Mike,undated (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cartwright, Floyd,undated (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cashen, George -1-and 3-year-old Boys,undated (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Casner, Mary Lou,undated (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Catcher, Chief Amos - I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Caulkins, Nelson,undated (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Centennial Association, Central State Normal School Building,June 26, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Centennial Association, Broadway Avenue View of Mount Pleasant,June 26, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Centennial Association, John W. Morrison Store,June 26, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Centennial Association, Main Street,June 26, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Central [Michigan University] Football Players,1942 (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Chaffee, Don - 1-year-old Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Chamberlain (Mrs.) - I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Chase, Fanny,undated (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Chippewa River,undated (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Christianson, (Mrs.) - Mrs. Christianson with 2 Children,undated (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Clare, Cecil - (Bruce) - 1st Communion (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Clare, Cecil - (Mark) - 1st Communion,1963 (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Clark, Larry (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cline Advertising Agency - Hanson's Milk - Milk Carton,July 17, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cline Advertising Agency - Ideal Cottage Cheese,undated (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cline Advertising Agency - vel-va-cote -Latex Flat Paint,December 26, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cline, Roy -Advertising Agency (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cluley, Wallace - 7-month-old Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 210)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Clymiers (Mrs.),undated (Box 1, Folder 211)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Coady, James - 1-and 3-year-olds,undated (Box 1, Folder 212)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Coady, Mary - I.D.,undated (Box 1, Folder 213)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cochran, Gary,undated (Box 1, Folder 214)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cochran, Joe - Academy Senior,September 29, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 215)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Coellner, Elaine -Copy,February 5, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 216)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Coellner, Elaine,December 14, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 217)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Conners, Bob - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 218)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Conners, Francis Thomas - Honorable Discharge from Navy,February 26, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 219)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Conners, Jim,undated (Box 1, Folder 220)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Conners, Jim - Baby Boy,undated (Box 1, Folder 221)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Conners, Jim - Wedding,undated (Box 1, Folder 222)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Conners, Jim, Sr. - Copy (2 envelopes),undated (Box 1, Folder 223)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cook, Bob - Wedding,undated (Box 1, Folder 224)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cook, Fritz,undated (Box 1, Folder 225)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cook, Steve,undated (Box 1, Folder 226)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cook, Theo -3-month-old,undated (Box 1, Folder 227)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cook, Theo - Girl,undated (Box 1, Folder 228)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cooley, Dick (Mrs.),undated (Box 1, Folder 229)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Cooley, Elaine,undated (Box 1, Folder 230)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Coon, Buelah (Mrs.) -Copy (4 envelopes),March 1, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 231)
  - 5 x 7 inch Negatives, A-G, Coppins, Emiel,undated (Box 1, Folder 232)